<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>http://sinha-raunak.github.io/</link>
      <atom:link href="http://sinha-raunak.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description></description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 23:28:04 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>http://sinha-raunak.github.io/img/icon-192.png</url>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://sinha-raunak.github.io/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>FamilyGAN: Generating Kin Face Images using Generative Adversarial Networks, ECCV 2020 Workshop</title>
      <link>http://sinha-raunak.github.io/publication/familygan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 23:28:04 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://sinha-raunak.github.io/publication/familygan/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation of Siamese Networks for Semantic Code Search, Preprint 2020</title>
      <link>http://sinha-raunak.github.io/publication/codesearch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 23:37:06 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://sinha-raunak.github.io/publication/codesearch/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visualization For Splitting An Application Into Modules (USPTO patent pending, 2020)</title>
      <link>http://sinha-raunak.github.io/publication/patent1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 23:42:43 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://sinha-raunak.github.io/publication/patent1/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Natural Language Code Search</title>
      <link>http://sinha-raunak.github.io/project/nl_codesearch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 23:51:59 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://sinha-raunak.github.io/project/nl_codesearch/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Structured understanding of programming languages, like C and Java, by linking them to the semantics of human-understandable (natural) languages would help understand code better. We are presently working on Natural Language Code Search and achieve an improvement of 16% in retrieval scores.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generating kin images using Generative Adversarial Networks</title>
      <link>http://sinha-raunak.github.io/project/familygan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 23:18:14 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://sinha-raunak.github.io/project/familygan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Establising the problem statement on generating images of kin (family members). FamilyGAN achieves ~2% variation in kin-verification scores for original and generated pairs. This indicates that the generated distribution successfully observes kin feature hierarchies.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recommending Microservices</title>
      <link>http://sinha-raunak.github.io/project/ms_recommendation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 23:51:49 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://sinha-raunak.github.io/project/ms_recommendation/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AuthorGAN: Improving GAN Reproducibility using a Modular GAN Framework</title>
      <link>http://sinha-raunak.github.io/project/authogan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 20:33:18 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://sinha-raunak.github.io/project/authogan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Generative models are becoming increasingly popular in the literature, with Gener- ative Adversarial Networks (GAN) being the most successful variant, yet. With this increasing demand and popularity, it is becoming equally difficult and challenging to implement and consume GAN models. A qualitative user survey conducted across 47 practitioners show that expert level skill is required to use GAN model for a given task, despite the presence of various open source libraries. In this research, we propose a novel system called AuthorGAN, aiming to achieve true democratization of GAN authoring. A highly modularized library agnostic repre- sentation of GAN model is defined to enable interoperability of GAN architecture across different libraries such as Keras, Tensorflow, and PyTorch. An intuitive drag-and-drop based visual designer is built using node-red platform to enable custom architecture designing without the need for writing any code. Five different GAN models are implemented as a part of this framework and the performance of the different GAN models are shown using the benchmark MNIST dataset.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AuthorGAN: Improving GAN Reproducibility using a Modular GAN Framework, NeurIPS 2019</title>
      <link>http://sinha-raunak.github.io/publication/authorgan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 19:09:32 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://sinha-raunak.github.io/publication/authorgan/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tranfering Adversarial Perturbation</title>
      <link>http://sinha-raunak.github.io/project/aml/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 20:04:15 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://sinha-raunak.github.io/project/aml/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Deep learning models have been shown to perform extremely well for many image based tasks. Such tasks include image classification, image generation, and image caption generation, etc. For such tasks deep learning methods have shown to understand the information present in images and make an intelligent decision.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A lot of what such models learn is dependent on the given data set. Is it actually possible to enhance information present in the data by adding perturbation and noise to the data? We are interested to find a possible answer for this question.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We propose an algorithm for transferring of data perturbation across different models and domains. We are interested in transferring adversarial data perturbations as attacks on the model&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Transfer learning to learn perturbations for a model. Adapting noise learned for one model, to another model.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintaining the visual appearance of data samples after
transferring perturbations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adapting noise with just one iteration of the dataset or 1-epoch (this reduces the computational complexity)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multi-label Triplet Embeddings for Image Annotation from User-Generated Tags</title>
      <link>http://sinha-raunak.github.io/project/mca/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 00:29:30 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://sinha-raunak.github.io/project/mca/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To predict (extract) semantic labels for a given image. This is achieved by using triplet loss on latent embedding (features) for images and text-labels.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>noWhinge</title>
      <link>http://sinha-raunak.github.io/project/dhcs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2019 20:25:11 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://sinha-raunak.github.io/project/dhcs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;noWhinge!s&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facial retouching detection using Subclass Restricted Boltzmann Machines</title>
      <link>http://sinha-raunak.github.io/project/sml/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 20:13:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://sinha-raunak.github.io/project/sml/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our project is to build and explore subclass Restricted Boltzmann Machines (subclass RBMs), a combination of Subclass Discriminant Analysis (SDA) and RBMs - extending the approach in [1]. To demonstrate the subclass RBM, we plan to use it for facial retouching detection problem, where we classify a given image of a face as unaltered or retouched. This is an important problem in face recognition domain since retouched photos can affect face recognition and thus, may pose a threat to security.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monocular SLAM</title>
      <link>http://sinha-raunak.github.io/project/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2018 20:24:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://sinha-raunak.github.io/project/cv/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Simultaneous location and mapping(SLAM) is the problem of creating a map of an unknown environment and simultaneously tracking agent’s location. Concepts of epipolar geometry give multi-view solution for this problem. Monocular SLAM is performing this task with a single camera. As simple hardware can be utilized, this reduces cost and hardware complexity. Multiple algorithms and benchmark datasets have been developed for studying this problem. Application of Monocular SLAM extend to domains like robotics, entertainment augmented reality), telepresence and more.
We explore various monocular SLAM algorithms: Parallel Tracking and Mapping(PTAM), Large-Scale Direct Monocular(LSD)SLAM and ORB-SLAM.
Initial Proposal: We would focus on evaluating performance on benchmark datasets and analyzing the results. We plan to use the algorithm with best performance on the benchmark dataset, on real-time data.
Updated proposal (after feedback): We would focus on analyzing the results of our algorithm on varying sequences (chosen from a benchmark dataset: TUM RGB-D so as to allow enough variations - we only use the RGB component of the data) and understand the successes and failure cases of our model.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Github Stack-Overflow User Recommendation System</title>
      <link>http://sinha-raunak.github.io/project/nlp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 20:30:23 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://sinha-raunak.github.io/project/nlp/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Trajectory of Basketball Shots</title>
      <link>http://sinha-raunak.github.io/project/ia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 20:30:39 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://sinha-raunak.github.io/project/ia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Detecting moving basketball using advanced image analysis techniques for segmentation and extraction. Mapping ball trajectory for predicting shot path.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recommendation System on MovieLens dataset</title>
      <link>http://sinha-raunak.github.io/project/movielense/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 23:52:23 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://sinha-raunak.github.io/project/movielense/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Almost all online services use a recommendation system in one way or other. Even though the field is widely explored, it still remains a challenging problem and a lot of research is still going on. We want to explore various advanced ML models by implementing those for a movie recommendation system. We believe working on this problem will give us a better understanding of ML concepts and give us a first hand experience of designing and debugging ML systems. The model will be trained using available ratngs and at testing time, it will predict ratings for a given (user,movie) pair.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
